(True Beauty)
Hello.
- Is this your second child? - Yes.
What a handsome young man!
It's actually a girl.
But Hee Kyung's so pretty.
Goodness, look how pretty she is.
She could enter a beauty pageant.
I knew since I was a kid
just by people's reactions...
that I'm ugly.
Grandpa!
Please take back that move.
- Just that last one. - Please?
No way, that's against the rules.
- Did you see that move? - No takebacks.
By the way, how is it that Ju Kyung...
only took after her mother's family?
If only she took after her dad too.
- She'll need plastic surgery. - Come on!
- Seriously? - Honey,
she must've been adopted or something.
- Grandpa! - You'll hurt her feelings.
All you need to do is get good grades,
got it?
Let the love as pure as gems...
bloom into the Flower of Hope.
Flowering Heart, Romantic Lips.
Makeup transformation!
Just like the cartoon character,
I once dreamed of magically...
transforming into a beautiful fairy.
Let the love as pure as gems...
bloom into the Flower of Hope.
Romantic Lips. Makeup transformation!
- What? - What is that?
- Who is she kidding? - What a joke.
She must think she's some fairy.
She's so full of herself.
She transformed into an ugly monster!
Die, you monster!
Guys!
But rather than a character
from a sweet cartoon...
("The Cursed Mask")
That's when I figured out...
I was more like a character
from a horror comic book...
born with a cursed face.
("The Cursed Mask")
Through the professor...
who only works his job
with no drive or energy,
the social injustice of
modern society is depicted.
If you take a look at
the following questions,
you'll find...
Boy, time sure did fly.
Don't forget your homework
that's due tomorrow.
Class is over.
- Sure. - Got it!
- Se Mi, here you go. - Yes.
Thanks.
Darn, my hair's all flat.
It serves you right for
resting your head on it.
- Fine, I'm sorry! - What is it?
Would you like to read this?
I'm not sure.
Would you like to listen to this?
Se Mi, can I try your lip tint?
Not even the best makeup will
make you as beautiful as her.
It's not for you to see,
so stop getting on my nerves.
Look at her.
What the... How pathetic.
Hey, Dumpling.
- Hey, Dumpling. - Hey, Dumpling.
Did you call me?
No one else in this class goes by Dumpling.
Don't just stand there and be on your way.
Right now? Got it.
There goes the errand girl. Unbelievable.
Dumpling, the errand girl.
Tell me about it.
2 with meat and 1 with kimchi, right?
Get your fried chicken.
- I... - We'll take two dumplings.
I was here first.
Get lost.
- Enjoy, boys. - Thanks!
- 2 with meat - And 1 with kimchi, right?
Yes.
Thank you.
Hey, there.
(Cafeteria, Store)
Is Hyun Bin not here yet?
(Plain flour)
Hey, you.
Hyun Bin.
What? Is this Crash?
You know right away.
This is a classic.
Ju Kyung,
you and I have the same taste in music.
Just a second.
He's so attractive.
Now that's what I'm talking about.
Oh, yes.
My heart needs to stop pounding.
Calm down.
- Yes, that's it. - Calm down.
Oh, yes!
- 1, 2! - Calm down already!
Sorry. What did you just say?
No, it was nothing.
- Take it from me if you can. - Hey.
Gosh, what's taking her so long?
Is she steaming the dumplings herself?
- My gosh, look at her. - What is it?
- What is it? - What?
Who is he?
Isn't he the cafeteria guy
who always hits on you?
I guess they have good
chemistry or something.
Nice! Yes, that's it!
- Enjoy. - Thank you.
Isn't Hyun Bin so attractive?
I'm not sure.
He told me he and I have
the same taste in music,
and he just smiled at me too.
Don't you think he's also interested in me?
I'm not sure.
I'm thinking of asking him out tomorrow.
Isn't that a great idea?
I'm... I'm not sure.
Hey, look at Ju Kyung.
She's wearing white
socks over black tights.
If I give you 10,000 dollars,
would you go out with her?
I won't go out with her even if
you give me 100,000 dollars.
I'm going to eat a little later.
What?
Keep moving.
- Enjoy. - Thank you.
Here you go.
There.
Enjoy.
Hyun Bin.
Can we meet tomorrow...
during lunchtime?
Tomorrow? Sure.
Look at Ju Kyung.
I can't believe she's hitting on him.
Can you put some strength into it?
Son, what are you doing outside?
Are you hungry? Do you want some fruit?
No.
Ju Kyung, why aren't you studying?
What did you do in the kitchen all weekend?
I just made something.
Do something about your grades, will you?
- Your grades got worse last time...
- Okay, I'll deal with it on my own.
Ju Kyung! I'm not done talking!
Just let her deal with it.
- Let's watch the show.
- Whom does she take after?
What?
- Massage my left shoulder too.
- Okay, you got it.
(Columbus Park)
(Can you at least give me
back the money I invested?)
Concentrate.
Okay. Just a second.
The door is open.
- My daughter, you're home. - Yes.
It's urgent. I need to go.
- The door is locked.
- Is it number 1 or number 2?
Number two.
I'm not done yet.
Do you want me to feed you my poop?
Go to the bathroom in the master bedroom.
- The master bedroom.
- You might poop your pants.
- Hold your bottom. - Okay.
- You'll poop your pants.
- Keep it clenched.
- My gosh. - Breathe.
Do the Lamaze breathing.
("Abandoned Kid 1", "Abandoned Kid 2")
(Metal Metal Band Concert Ticket)
(To Hyun Bin)
You're a fool.
You're a fool who doesn't know how I feel.
And I'm a fool who only has eyes for you.
"You fool,
why wouldn't I know how you feel?"
Oh, my goodness!
Will you go out with me?
Will you please turn down the music?
I'd rather go blind.
What's with her?
(Se Yeon, you will always be in my heart.)
(Happy birthday,
Se Yeon. I hope you're happy in paradise.)
Se Yeon's fans are so weird.
Didn't they badmouth him before he died?
Why are they suddenly acting
like they're sad about his death?
What a bunch of hypocrites.
I'm going to confess my
love to the guy I like today.
I'm really nervous.
Wish me luck.
I swear I'm really nervous.
You're so brave. Good luck.
I hope he also likes you back.
(- You're so brave. Good luck.
- I hope he also likes you back.)
My gosh.
Hey, careful.
Stop pushing.
My gosh, seriously.
Hey, it's Se Mi.
- What? Really? - Where?
It's Se Mi.
Make way.
She's so pretty in real life.
This is crazy.
Get up so Se Mi can sit down.
Se Mi, sit here.
She's really pretty.
Is she going to sit there?
What are you doing?
Sorry.
My gosh.
- Seriously? - I'll go buy dumplings.
What was that?
Look at what she brought.
A dumpling vending machine?
What is this?
- I don't know. - Cookies?
It's so ugly. How embarrassing.
She really put in a lot of effort.
"You're a fool. You're a fool
who doesn't know how I feel."
"I'm also a fool."
My gosh, what a cheesy line.
- Hey. - Yes?
Is Dumpling going to ask him out today?
Oh, well...
Why can't you talk properly?
I totally get why she's friends with her.
- Hyun Bin. - Hey, Se Mi. What's up?
Do you have time?
Do you have something to say?
Well...
By any chance, are you dating Ju Kyung?
What? Why do you ask?
You have no idea how
shocked I was when I heard that.
Compared to a good-looking guy like you,
she's someone who's way down there...
that doesn't even deserve you.
You guys are on
completely different levels.
Yes, of course.
You're too nice to her
because you're so kind.
I bet that's why she
thinks she deserves you.
Well, yes. I tend to be pretty kind.
To be honest,
when I heard about you and Ju Kyung,
I got really upset.
I'm the one at fault for
making you feel that way.
I'm a real jerk. I really am.
Hyun Bin, don't do that to yourself.
You'll hurt your handsome face.
Well, I guess I'll see you next time,
Hyun Bin.
Next time? When? Today?
I have time right now.
- Pretty soon. - Okay, Se Mi.
I'll send you a DM. I'll see you soon.
Sure, Hyun Bin.
I'll contact you.
That was so easy.
How naive of him.
(Morning Care)
(Cosmetology License)
There you go. It looks perfect.
They are exactly the same.
They're like mirror images.
As always, you're the best.
- May I stay for coffee? - Yes, of course.
Okay. Let's see.
It came out too light last time.
The trend is to look natural.
If I spend money on it, I want it to show.
Gosh. All right.
Leave it to me.
Why doesn't your handsome
husband come by anymore?
I don't know. He's always on his phone now.
Who knows what he's up to?
Is he having an affair?
He can have affairs if he wants.
As long as he doesn't
get into money trouble.
Do you want your eyebrows done?
Where's Lim Jae Pil's wife?
What is this?
They're concert tickets,
cookies that I baked,
- and... - And what?
And...
my heart.
I like you.
What?
Are you asking me out?
I'm Hyun Bin. Wang Hyun Bin.
Sorry?
Yes.
What? Did you think I'd
agree to go out with you?
You said last time that I was a good kid,
- and that we have similar taste. - Hey.
I was being nice because I felt bad
that you were an outcast. But what?
If you don't have the looks,
at least have smarts.
Are you that dense?
If you have time to do this,
look at a mirror instead.
Did you see that?
Oh no. Poor Ju Kyung.
That was our school's ugliest girl...
asking a guy out.
Applause.
Finally, let's hear how it
felt to be rejected so coldly.
- Let's hear it. - Let's hear it.
Amazing. You look insanely ugly.
Look at her head.
- Stop it.
- Hurry. You were on camera already.
Tell us.
I said to stop it.
- Hey. - "I said to stop it."
Hey, you. How dare you hit her?
Do you want to die?
Why do you guys hate me so much?
Why do you hate me?
I did nothing wrong to you.
Why do you hate me this much?
Hey.
Want me to tell you?
Because you're ugly.
- You got ugly on you. - You're right.
Don't touch me.
- I forgot. - Don't touch me.
- Darn it. - Stop it.
Do that again.
- Stop it. - How did it look when she fell?
"I said to stop it."
- Hey. Where is she going?
- She's running away.
'I said to stop it."
- I can't stand her. - Whatever.
(Yongpa High School Community)
The guy's butt too. She's
ugly and has bad taste.
She's the ugliest in our school.
Where did she get the guts?
I'd be too humiliated to
come to school if I were her.
If you have time to do this,
look at a mirror instead.
If you don't have the looks,
at least have smarts.
Are you that dense?
Because you're ugly.
Silence!
Here's the star of our community.
- Ugly! - Ugly!
Hey, look.
No one likes me.
How can I come to school tomorrow?
(In Loving Memory Of Jeong Se Yeon)
(Happy 18th Birthday In Loving
Memory Of Jeong Se Yeon)
How tragic.
He would be turning 18.
I...
I don't want to die.
Gosh, it's cold.
What a relief.
What on earth was that?
My glasses...
Where are they?
Where are my glasses?
I can't see anything without them.
What were you up to just now?
Were you going to jump?
Are you insane?
Have you lost your mind?
What could be hard enough
to make you want to die?
How could you give
up on your life like this?
I wasn't going to jump...
You should try to overcome
the difficulties instead.
Have you even considered how devastated...
your loved ones would be?
- I... - Someone...
might forever live in guilt...
for not being able to save you.
Understand?
There's nothing you can do...
for a dead person.
So don't die.
Why aren't you coming?
Is it to jump once I leave?
No, that's not it.
It's just...
Excuse me...
My glasses...
Wait a second!
(Elevator Maintenance)
What is it?
Is it out of order?
Wait for me, sir!
Please wait for me.
Wait for me.
You knocked my glasses off
me and now I can't see a thing.
I'm blind without them.
Without them,
I can't even tell poop and doenjang apart.
Darn it.
Excuse me. Are you still there?
He must really be gone.
Darn, my life!
What?
I see you haven't left.
Take my hand and stand.
Sure.
- Watch your hands! - I...
It was never my intention to grope you.
Get on my back instead.
Thank you.
I know I'm heavier than I seem, mister.
You look heavy too.
And who are you calling "mister"?
Excuse me.
I have something to ask.
Mister, why were you at the rooftop...
Lady, stop whispering, will you?
My voice echoing is scary, that's why.
Also, I'm not some old lady.
Can't you see I'm in a school uniform?
Did you perhaps...
know someone who was
at the rooftop like I was?
It just makes sense.
You pulled me back to
safety but then got all angry.
I was wondering if
anyone around you died...
Say another word...
and I'll leave you behind.
Darn, she's heavy.
Heave-ho, heave-ho!
- Lady! - Okay, I won't say a word.
My lips are sealed.
(Elevator Maintenance)
Sir, wasn't the elevator out of order?
It was just getting a maintenance check.
Didn't you hear the announcement?
All right.
Maybe we should've waited.
Hey, mister!
Again with the "mister"?
What?
Well,
I know I'm not in a position to say this,
but cheer up.
The one who died...
won't want those left
behind to suffer for too long.
It's why you should be happy.
You must, okay?
Please take me to Bucheon, please.
Why go up there anyway...
when you're not even brave enough to jump?
I just got those glasses.
Gosh, Mom will be mad.
You'll be transferred to
voicemail after the beep...
and will be charged.
Mom, I was hoping to hear your voice.
Actually, no.
It's better this way.
I won't be able to die
if I hear your voice.
Thank you...
for bringing me to this world
and raising me for 18 years.
I promise to be born as
your daughter in my next life.
That's when we'll meet again.
When we do,
I hope I get to have a
face everyone calls pretty.
Oh, no.
What if Mom checked the voicemail?
I hope she hasn't listened to it yet.
Why isn't she picking up?
- Sir, can you drive faster? - Sure.
Please pick up. Please.
(My daughter, Ju Kyung)
Mom, please. Take her to her room.
Let me go. You darn punk.
They found a ship loaded with
treasures near Ulleung Island?
- You actually believed that?
- If you think about it,
it's not entirely impossible.
Back in 1905,
during the Russo-Japanese War...
I don't care about the Russo-Japanese War.
I'll show you what a war is,
you son of a gun!
No, wait! Mom, please!
- Grab her! - Let me go.
- No, don't.
- A famous ship sunk during the war.
It's a historical fact.
My life is about to sink
underwater because of you.
Do you think 500,000 dollars is easy money?
How could you invest that much money?
You're 50 years old,
and we're still paying rent!
Dad, hurry up and apologize! Come on!
- My gosh. - Hurry!
Honey, I'm sorry.
Hyun Sook, I'm truly sorry.
- Forgive me just this once.
- Don't expect me to forgive you.
I'll kill you today and get
myself locked up in jail.
- No, please! - Mom. Mom.
- My gosh. I'm sorry. - Dad, this way.
- I'm sorry. - Mom.
- Wait. Mom. - Stop right there.
- Here. - My gosh.
Get over here. Now.
- Stop it. - You little...
- My gosh. - There!
Seriously?
The one who died won't
want those left behind...
to suffer for too long.
It's why you should be happy.
Mom. Mom.
I'd rather just die instead.
Mom! Mom, don't die!
Hey, you're here.
I can't possibly leave you guys behind.
Let's all die together. Let's do that.
I won't ever say that again,
so please don't cry.
How can I not cry?
My darn life.
It's all because I was born ugly.
Hee Kyung and Ju Young
were born with Dad's looks.
But I wasn't. That's why.
- What? - It's true.
I'm ugly because I take after you.
What did you say?
Will you please get a
grasp of what's going on?
Ju Kyung, shut it.
I won't die, so let me get plastic surgery.
That will solve everything.
Have you lost your mind? Why
do you want plastic surgery?
Do you want to get kicked out?
You're better off with a pretty
daughter than an ugly one.
Don't make things worse.
Just go. Get out of my sight!
- Come on. - Let me get plastic surgery.
- Get over here.
- Let me get plastic surgery.
I'm the only one who
takes after your looks.
- Let me get plastic surgery.
- Will you please be quiet?
(Friends)
(Hye Min)
(Hye Min, are you up? Today's the big day!)
(I'm so nervous about asking him out.)
I guess I was the only one
who thought we were friends.
Starting from tomorrow,
I'll really be all alone.
I want to drop out of school.
Ju Kyung.
Ju Kyung, are you sleeping?
I was just about to sleep.
Mom and I are off to have
soju. Get some sleep, okay?
I shouldn't have left that voice message.
It only ended up breaking Mom's heart.
Back when...
I bought our apartment,
I was so excited that I
couldn't sleep for days.
- Are you going to sell our house?
- What else can I do?
We can't even find a
tenant for our old house,
so we won't be able
to sell it at a good price.
I'll sell this house, pay off his debt,
and move into the old house.
Don't do that. I'll get my
severance pay in advance...
- and look into getting a loan...
- Forget it.
I should be the one to take
care of my husband's mess.
You kids did nothing wrong.
Tell Dad to come back home.
You shouldn't have kicked him
out in his underwear in this weather.
Whatever. I don't care
where he sleeps tonight.
(Beauty Salon, Pandora Shop)
I'm sorry.
No, don't!
(I'm going to confess my
love to the guy I like today.)
(I swear I'm really nervous.)
- You're so brave.
- I hope he also likes you back.
- Keep us updated.
- Did you ask him out today?
Come on. Tell us what happened.
Hey, guys. To be honest, I got rejected.
I guess people don't like me...
because I'm ugly.
- Oh, dear. - Try getting better grades.
Get plastic surgery. Leave
it to a plastic surgeon.
I'm not smart,
and I'm not allowed to get plastic surgery.
Do you wear makeup? You
can overcome it with makeup.
Click on this link.
(Miraculous makeover with makeup,
I hope you all become prettier.)
(Miraculous makeover with makeup)
(How to put on makeup for the guy you like)
Oh, my gosh.
This is it.
Oh, gosh.
- My gosh. - What the...
Why are they staring at me?
Is it because of the video?
Or is it because I actually got prettier?
This is awesome.
I need to capture this.
Hey. Did you use a black
marker to do your eyeliner?
- Look at her.
- Oh my gosh. I want a picture.
Now, I must save this.
Look at that.
- Awesome. - Look here.
Look.
Didn't your parents say
anything when you left home?
- Look here. - My gosh.
This is awesome.
Hey, smile.
Smile.
Hey. Smile for us.
Yes. I need to sell it quickly.
We're in a bit of a rush.
As quickly as possible, please.
Mom.
Oh my gosh.
What did you do to your face?
Are you trying to give
your mom a heart attack?
I put on makeup. Is it very weird?
Makeup?
That's stage makeup. For a ghost.
Were you filming a horror movie?
Wash that off right now.
I'm too humiliated to go to school.
Mom. I want to transfer.
Please let me transfer.
Gosh. You'll have to transfer
even if you don't want to.
We're moving back to our old place,
so you have to transfer.
Really? For real?
Yes!
Why are you so dense?
Why? I'm on cloud nine right now.
I'm transferring out.
Are you taunting me right now?
I'm home.
Hi.
Oh, my eyes!
You almost killed me with your face.
Ju Young, you want to die?
Why would you kill my precious son? Why?
A horror movie?
If I go to school like this...
Does my makeup look really weird?
I want to get rid of my
outcast image before I transfer.
Please help.
No, please.
- Is that a monster?
- Clean up your eyebrows first.
- They look like caterpillars.
- Caterpillars...
They do look like caterpillars.
Check out her third post.
- It'll help. - A post?
Hi, beauties. I'll share a tip on
making your eyes look bigger.
(Hi, beauties. I'll share a tip on
making your eyes look bigger.)
1, 2, 3.
(Eat your heart out, boys)
Seriously? Awesome.
Yes, this is it.
It was a huge incident that drove
Mom and Dad nearly to a divorce,
but for me, it was hope for a new life.
In makeup, the lips complete the look.
I will use this tint.
What do you think? My dear Selebies.
So? Were you reborn today as a new you?
A new me?
Keep your faith in me,
Selena, and follow me.
Oh no.
Oh no. No.
I'm going to draw it in anyway,
so it's okay.
Stay calm.
Aren't you going to pack?
What has she been doing?
Focus.
Awesome.
(You're the Demon)
"You're the Demon".
- What? - "You're the Demon".
- What? - The new volume is out, right?
Yes. I got it earlier,
so I put it in the bookcase.
You haven't been here in a while.
He hasn't changed at
all in the past 10 years.
Look.
- The first page was ripped out. - What?
Maybe the first kids...
- who borrowed it ripped it out. - Why?
That is despicable.
But can't you skip the first
page and start with page two?
I think you can follow
the story even without it.
Do you sing the national anthem
starting with the second verse?
Do you skip the first
half of a soccer match...
and watch only the second half?
You must skip January
and work hard from February.
It doesn't affect your age.
You're so right.
I'll order a new one right away.
I'll call you as soon as it arrives,
so when it comes tomorrow...
He really hasn't changed.
Ju Kyung? Wake up. We're almost there.
- Dad... - Okay?
(Prince Comics)
(Comics)
Darn it.
Oh no.
Sorry.
Chocolate brown contacts. In.
Apply a soft brown shadow
to provide depth to the eyelids.
Apply cocoa shadow under the eyes.
This will widen your eyes.
Then finish off the makeup.
(Lim Ju Kyung, Yongpa High School)
Attention-grabbing first
impression makeup complete.
I hate this house.
I worked so hard to get out.
I take a step forward in life
but return to where I started.
That's eight years down the drain.
So you're eight years younger?
- What? - Come on.
Isn't it nice to be back?
Doesn't it remind you of our
romantic days as newlyweds?
Romantic, my foot.
Ju Kyung, come down for breakfast...
I'm good. I don't have an appetite anyway.
What do you mean you don't...
Who on earth are you?
What do you mean? Anyway,
I'm off to school!
Gosh, who on earth is she?
- She's stunning! - Who?
- I haven't seen her before. - Me neither.
Can you believe it?
- She's beautiful? - No way!
This can't be real.
(Saebom High School, Lim Ju Kyung)
She's absolutely beautiful.
Aphrodite is reborn.
I'm...
beautiful?
- My gosh. - I can't believe it.
Can this be true?
My gosh, she's stunning.
Where's the teachers' office?
What on earth?
She's beautiful.
(Stop pretending to be ladylike.)
(Says the one pretending
to be a model student.)
(- What? - Why you...)
Although you didn't live so far away,
I bet you haven't fully adjusted yet.
I lived here until I was 10, so I'm good.
I'm glad to hear that.
Here. Starting today,
you go to Saebom High School.
Right.
(Lim Ju Kyung, Saebom High School)
I hear that the new student
used to be at the top of her class.
It must be her.
Let me see her grades.
Doesn't she already seem
like one to have great grades?
(Grades)
Forget it.
This must be the student
who was at the top of his class.
See? Doesn't he look like one...
to have great grades?
We'll get going then.
Of course. Introduce
yourself to your classmates.
He's the vice-principal,
but don't be bothered by his words.
Grades don't always mean the world.
Sure.
If it isn't the top of our junior class!
No wonder it suddenly got brighter in here.
Gosh, he's handsome.
See? Can one be more charming when bowing?
- Here you go. - Thanks.
Why does that voice sound familiar?
But please ask the
class president next time.
- Sure. - Never have I come across...
such a handsome being before.
Soo Ho.
This is a transfer
student joining our class.
Could you escort her?
Must I? Really?
Yes, you must.
- Follow him out. - Sure.
Wait for me.
Handsome and top of the class?
I guess life really is unfair.
Wait... Soo Ho!
I thought this foundation didn't rub off!
Are we close? Why are
you acting like we are?
Soo Ho, I mean... Are you free?
- No, I'm busy. - It won't take long.
I have something to say to you.
- You have three seconds. - What?
- One... - Soo Ho, I mean...
- 2, 3, time's up. - I've always liked you.
- No. - Then please accept this.
(Lee Soo Ho)
Wait a second. My gosh.
My face! What if my makeup's gone?
1, 2...
- Hey, Soo Ho. - Hey, friend.
Just a second.
What's that on your
back? Is it a new trend?
How sophisticated.
What is that on his back? Makeup?
I'm glad my eye makeup is still there.
Hey!
What's his problem?
But I only bought this recently.
Joining our class as of
today is Lim Ju Kyung.
Would you like to say hello?
Hi, it's nice to meet you.
You're beautiful!
Is this for real?
Being pretty made a difference...
regarding how the kids look at me.
Welcome!
All except one person.
We're now a better-looking class.
Ahn Hyun Kyu, don't you say that...
because you're all beautiful in my eyes.
You look beautiful from a distance
and even more stunning up close.
Must you be so cheesy?
I know you're not aware
of how beautiful you are,
but being 18 makes you the
most stunning people ever,
so don't try so hard to look
better. Especially you, Soo Ah.
Got it.
Must you be so serious all the time?
Ju Kyung, let's see. The
seat next to Soo Ho's is vacant.
I have bad eyesight, you see.
Is that so? The seat belongs
to another student on a break,
but sit behind Soo Ah.
Sure.
What's today's first class? Mine, right?
- Open your books then. - Got it.
Do you all remember the poets...
who were members of Cheongnokpa?
- No! - No!
Of course,
you don't remember. So Cheongnokpa...
consisted of poets who wrote
about nature that embodied...
- Here. - eternity and humanity.
- Thanks. - Pak Tu Jin, Park Mok Wol,
and Cho Chi Hun got together
and published their first book...
titled "Cheonglokjib".
Good job, everyone. Don't
forget to do your assignments.
- Bye! - Good day.
Gosh, this is awkward.
I saw you at the front gate today.
Really?
Hi, new girl.
Hi.
Can I get your number?
Right.
Are you on Stargram? What's your username?
I don't have a Stargram account.
Why not? Are you trying to be mysterious?
Followers will pile up the
second you create one.
I love the colour of your
lips. Which lip tint do you use?
Oh, really? My lip tint...
She's gorgeous...
and apparently with no makeup on.
Here you go.
Thanks.
Hey, Soo Jin.
She's my best friend, Kang Soo Jin.
I've been calling her
the queen of our school,
but that might change now that you're here.
I guess you have competition now.
Don't pat my behind like that.
Ju Kyung, right? It's good to meet you.
Same here.
You're gorgeous though.
Are you a K-pop idol trainee?
She talks a lot, doesn't she? I
hope you don't find it annoying.
It's fine.
I get that it was my fault,
but how can he throw this at my face?
I'll wash it off for you, darn it.
Why won't this come off?
It's waterproof. Oh, no.
Gosh, I can't believe it.
Sorry.
You know, I can have this dry cleaned...
Toss it in the trash.
How can I throw this away?
I'll return it to you spotless!
Ju Kyung, what's with Soo Ho?
I got something on his jacket,
and he told me to throw it away.
The jerk's at it again.
That's how he normally is.
The handsome psychopath.
- Really? - Yes.
So he's a cocky jerk.
- Ju Kyung, dumplings...
- Sure, I'll get them for you.
That's not it.
I was asking you to join us.
- Together? - Yes.
I can't believe you snagged her
before she could make friends.
What's wrong with that? She's mine, anyway.
You sure are quick when
it comes to making friends.
So Ju Kyung, what do you enjoy?
I like heavy metal and
horror comic books but...
I like reading books
and listening to music.
What kind of music? I'm
a huge fan of Eighteen.
And I love spicy food.
I really like spicy food as well.
Really? That's great!
Then why don't we eat
tteokbokki after school today...
to congratulate our
first day of being friends?
Sure. That sounds nice.
We're friends.
- Doo Jin, will you join us? - Sure.
But it's Soo Jin,
not Doo Jin. Say my name properly.
Okay, Soo Jin, you smarty-pants
with the second-highest grades.
Soo Ho and Soo Jin always compete
to get the best grades in our year.
She's not only pretty,
but she's also smart.
Don't tell me you're smart too.
I have bad grades.
That's perfect.
Ju Kyung, just be a pretty girl like me.
But I'm not pretty.
Soo Ah, you really need to study.
- Why? - Let me help you study.
- No, I'm not interested.
- You need to get better grades.
Ju Kyung, let's study together.
There we go. You can eat it now.
Okay.
Let's enjoy.
- What do you think? - It's really good.
- It's good, right? - Yes.
But it's a bit spicy.
Doo Jin, please. Just this once.
- No, let's go next time. - Come on.
- Just 10 minutes.
- My mom will get angry at me.
Then five minutes. It won't take long.
I don't have five minutes.
Ju Kyung, let's try everything that's here.
You too, Soo Jin.
(A beginner in life,
A pro at playing games)
Did you see that? I have the highest score.
Didn't I get any?
That's the boss.
Come on.
Keep going.
Keep going! Nice! Look at that!
This is so fun.
Ju Kyung, you should try it too.
Is this how you do it?
Yes, good.
You're pretty good.
You look really cute.
Let's begin.
Look over here.
Ju Kyung,
is it your first time taking photos?
- You need to look here. - Oh, there?
Pose.
In the past, no matter how hard I tried,
I could never have what I truly wanted.
Friends.
But I have friends now.
Gosh.
Get up.
Why are you overdoing it?
You haven't been here in a while.
So I can get some good sleep.
You're having trouble sleeping again?
It looks like you've gotten worse.
Then I'll help you knock out tonight.
This won't knock me out.
Hey, stop. That's enough.
(Soo Ah has invited Soo
Jin and Ju Kyung to the chat.)
(Soo Ah: Did you guys go home safely?)
Is this the group chat
that everyone always...
talks about?
I got invited to a group chat.
Did you guys go home safely?
Yes, what about you, Soo Jin?
- Soo Jin rarely checks her phone.
- Oh, I see.
By the way, I have a Stargram account now.
My ID is imzoo...
Nice. I'll follow you right now.
I'm studying with my tutor.
Here are the photos we took
today. Just download what you want.
Ju Young, what are you doing?
I know you're my sister,
but you're seriously so ugly.
- What? - Come on.
People at school think you're pretty.
Should I show them this photo?
Ju Young, delete it right now.
Get over here. Are you serious right now?
- Come here. - You want this?
Delete it. Delete it
right now. I'm serious.
- You punk. - "You punk."
- Do you have a death wish?
- "Do you have a death wish?"
What's the matter? This
is how you normally look.
Is this what you're looking
for? You're too slow.
Watch your left.
- Get off me. - You're dead.
Listen, young lady.
Let's keep our manners.
I feel a chill behind my back.
It's as if a dagger just
pierced through my chest.
But don't worry.
My hands move faster than
what the human eye can see.
Get over here!
My neck hurts! Get off me!
(Insert passcode)
Do you think I'm dumb?
What do you want?
The newly released volume
of "You're the Demon".
Then will you delete it?
That depends on how you behave.
Do you have a death wish?
Which photo should I upload?
Stop.
I'll add something on top of that.
You can have the new volume
and a pack of instant cup noodles.
Deal.
What a relief.
I'm following you now. I
see you uploaded a photo.
My gosh, you already got tons of likes.
Oh, really?
- Can we be Stargram friends?
- You're so beautiful.
Can you follow me too?
- You're really pretty.
- I got over 100 likes.
- You're gorgeous. - She's a real beauty.
I can't believe they think I'm beautiful.
This is absurd.
What if people from our
school see me like this?
(Prince Comics)
My goodness,
this place hasn't changed at all.
I wonder if the owner is still the same.
(Prince Comics)
Gosh, it's exactly the same.
Welcome.
Mister, you're still here.
- Who... - Don't you remember me?
Ju Kyung?
Yes.
You're finally back.
Your mom told me you guys moved back here.
Gosh, how long has it been?
I think it's been about eight years.
Has it been that long already?
My gosh, you've grown so
big. You haven't changed at all.
Yes, I'm still ugly.
I was going to say you're still so cute.
This one's fun.
The smell of comic books.
The stuff I scribbled
on the wall is still here.
(Lim Ju Kyung's spot. Sit without
permission, and get a hairy butt!)
This is what I'm talking about.
No one has a horror
collection quite as big as theirs.
Where is it?
Found it.
I was here first.
I grabbed it first.
Lee Soo Ho?
You.
I'm done for.
(True Beauty)
I'll make sure he doesn't
think I'm Lim Ju Kyung.
What if he knows?
Did you do something wrong?
He'll feel too sorry for
me to spread rumours.
Hey. We've met, haven't we?
What an outrageous coincidence.
Are you and Soo Ho going out?
- Now? - You have something for me.
- Bring it. - The no-makeup Ju Kyung?
The full-makeup Ju Kyung?
What am I supposed to bring him?
>>>>oakislandtk
www.opensubtitles.org